The Guide to the American Short Line Railroad Association records, 1912-1971
American Short Line Railroad Association records, 1912-1971
- Non- member and Inactive Member Files, 1913-1964.
  - Milstead Railroad LaGrange, Georgia and Milstead, Georgia; June 22, 1921 to Mar. 12, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Milwaukee Electric Railway and Transport Co. Milwaukee, Wisconsin; Feb. 1, 1923 to July 12, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, Reports, Map
  - Minneapolis and St. Louis Railroad Minneapolis, Minnesota; Jan. 21, 1921 to Dec. 27, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 10-13)
    Reports, Correspondence, Memos, Booklets, News articles, Map
  - Mississippi and Alabama Railroad Leakesville, Mississippi; Apr. 23, 1918 to Aug. 2, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 14-15)
  - Mississippian Railroad Amory, Mississippi; Aug. 16, 1923 to Apr. 8, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Missouri and Arkansas Railway Harrison, Arkansas; June 20, 1932 to Dec. 12, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 17-18)
    Reports, News articles, Correspondence, Blueprint
  - Monessen Southwestern Railway Pennsylvania; Apr. 9, 1956 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Montana, Wyoming and Southern Railroad Belfry, Montana; Mar. 27, 1917 to Mar. 1, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    Reports, News Article, Correspondence, Sketch
  - Monticello and Port Jervis Railroad Monticello (?) New York; Nov. 6, 1957 to Nov. 8, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Montour Railroad Pittsborg, Penna; Apr. 14, 1920 to Feb. 4, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    Reports, Correspondence, Notes
  - Montpelier and Wells River Railroad Montpelier Vermont; Jan. 1, 1925 to Jan. 6, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Mound City and Eastern Railway New York, New York and Long Lake, South Dakota; July 19, 1927 to Feb. 2, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    Correspondence, Photos, Report
  - Municipality of East Troy Wisconsin East Troy, Wisconsin; Oct. 27, 1949 to Jan. 11, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Murfreesboro-Nashville Railroad Murfreesboro, Arkansas; Dec. 16, 19 32 to Sept. 23, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 26-27)
    Reports, Map
  - Nacoadoches and Southeastern Railroad Shreveport, Louisiana; Dec. 3, 1918 to July 7, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 1-3)
    Reports, Maps, Correspondence
  - Nashville, Chattanoogao and St. Louis Railroad Nashville, Tennessee; Sept. 10, 1951 to Sept. 16, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Natchez, Urania and Ruston Railroad Urania, Louisiana; Apr. 28, 1919 to Jan. 16, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
  - Nelson and Albemarle (N and A) Railway Atlanta, Georgia; Nov. 1, 1920 to Jan. 21, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 7-9)
  - New Haven and Dunbar Railroad Scranton, Pennsylvania; Sept. 5, 1952 to Apr. 8, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - New Jersey, Indiana, and Illinois Railroad St. Louis, Missouri; June 17, 1959 to Nov. 2, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    Notices, Reports, Correspondence
  - Newport News Dry Dock Newport News, Virginia; Oct. 11, 1957 to Nov. 19, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, Print
  - North Carolina State Ports Wilmingtan, North Carolina; Nov. 10, 1955 to Nov. 16, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Northern Railroad of New Jersey Englewood, New Jersey; May 9, 1940 to Dec. 8, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Oakdale and Scribner Railroad, Nebraska Nebraska?; Aug. 31, 1915 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Ogden Union Stock Yards Co. Ogden, Utah; Jan. 1, 1946 to Dec. 30, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Ohio and Morenci Railroad Springfield, Ohio; Aug. 14, 1933 to July 2, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Ohio River Railway Pomeroy, Ohio; Apr. 26, 1929 to July 27, 1937 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    Notice, Correspondence
  - Oneida and Western (O and W) Railroad Oneida, Tennessee; June 17, 1918 to Apr. 12, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 19-22)
  - Osage Railway Webb City, Oklahoma and; Nov. 23, 1921 to Sept. 27, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Owens Valley Railroad Culver City, California (?); n.d. (Box 40, Folder 24)
    Business Card
  - Pacific Electric Railway Los Angeles County, Calif; Jan. 10, 1958 to Dec. 24, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Parkway Industrial Railroad Co. Cincinnate, Ohio; Jan. 18, 1946 to Feb. 12, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 26-27)
  - Peabody Short Line Railroad East St. Louis, Illinois; July 10, 1924 to Aug. 18, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    Reports, Correspondence, Article
  - Peoria and Eastern Railway line runs from Peoria, Illinois to Indianapolis, Indiana; July 7, 1952 to Jan. 28, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Petaluma and Santa Rosa Railroad San Rafael, Calif; Mar. 10, 1947 to Aug. 25, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Pioneer and Fayette Railroad Pioneer, Ohio; Jan. 18, 1934 to Dec. 23, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Portland Cement See Volunteer Portland Cement for Info; n.d. (Box 40, Folder 32)
    Cross-reference box 43, f.f. 22
  - Portland Electric Power Co. Portland, Oregon; Sept. 27, 1935 to Sept. 4, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    Application, Correspondence
  - Portland Traction Co. Portland, Oregon; Mar. 20, 1947 to May 24, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Potomac Edison Company Frederick, Maryland; Sept. 27, 1935 to Aug. 31, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 35-36)
    Reports, Correspondence, News article
  - Preston Railroad Pittsburg, Pennci, moved to Crellin, Maryland; Mar. 24, 1919 to 19-8, 1936 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Raleigh-Rolesville Railroad WakeCounty, North Carolina; Apr. 17, 1951 to July 21, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Red River and Gulf Railroad Long Leaf, Louisiana; Mar. 6, 1914 to July 12, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 3-4)
  - Rio Grande Southern Railroad Durango, Colorado; Oct. 23, 1923 to Apr. 8, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    Reports, News article, Correspondence
  - Rock Island Southern Railway Rock Island, Illinois; May 14, 1918 to May 23, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Rockingham Railroad Rockingham, North Carolina; Oct. 3, 1913 to Nov. 25, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Rock Port, Langdon and Northern Railway Rock Port, Mississippi; Feb. 11, 1918 to Apr. 25, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Rockton-Rion Railway Rion, South Carolina; Feb. 12, 1932 to Oct. 1, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 9-10)
  - Rowlesburg and Southern Railroad Erwin, West Virginia; Dec. 5, 1919 to Feb. 8, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 11-12)
    Correspondence, Report, Financial statements
  - St. Joseph Railway St. Joseph, Missouri; Aug. 10, 1920 to May 28, 1936 (Box 41, Folder 13-14)
    Correspondence, Reports, Stenographic manuscript
  - St. Joseph Terminal Railroad St. Joseph, Missouri; Aug. 11, 1933 to May 28, 1936 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - St. Louis and O'Fallon Railway St. Louis, Missouri; Sept. 21, 1934 to July 2, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 16-17)
  - St. Louis and Troy Railroad Troy, Missouri; Nov. 8, 1932 to Dec. 7, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 18-19)
    Correspondence, Reports, Financial schedules
  - Salt Lake Rail and Bus Terminal Co. Salt Lake City, Utah; Dec. 4, 1946 to May 13, 1947 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, Notes, Exhibits
  - Salt Lake and Utah Railroad Salt Lake City, Utah; Oct. 21, 1932 to Mar. 12, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 21-22)
    Correspondence, Transcript, Reports, ICC petitions
  - San Diego and Arizona Eastern Railway San Francisco, Calif; June 11, 1921 to Nov. 3, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 23-24)
    Reports, Correspondence, Article, Photo
  - San Francisco and Napa Valley Railroad Napa, California; Apr. 1, 1921 to Mar. 7, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 25-26)
  - San Manuel Arizona Railroad runs from San Manuel to Hayden, Arizona; Feb. .5, 1954 to Feb. 5, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Sanford and Eastern Railroad Boston, Mass; Apr. 2, 1962 to Nov. 5, 1920 (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    Reports, Correspondence, Statistical data
  - Saratoga and Schuylerville Railroad Boston, Mass; July 10, 1945 to Mar. 7, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, Reports, Memo
  - Satan's Kingdom Railroad runs from Collinsville to New Hartford, [UNK]; Mar. 10, 1954 to Mar. 12, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Smithfield Terminal Railway Newport New, Virginia; Oct. 11, 1946 to Dec. 16, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - South Central Railroad Amite, Louisiana; Sept. 15, 1955 to Mar. 23, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - South Omaha Terminal Railway Co. Omaha, Nebraska; Sept. 2, 1953 to Sept. 8, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - South Shore Railway Baton Rouge, Louisiana; Sept. 23, 1940 to Apr. 1, 1952 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Southeastern Railroad Paoli, Pennsylvania & Atlanta, Georgia; Aug. 8, 1947 to [9-20, 1962] (Box 42, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, ICC application
  - Spaulding Pulp and Paper Co. Newburg, Oregon[UNK]; Mar. 9, 1961 to Mar. 2, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Springfield Terminal Railway Chicago, Illinois; Apr. 1919 to Feb. 7, 1951 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Steward and Beutelschies Spurrums from Ft. Smith & Van Buren, Okla; Feb. 2, 1943 to Mar. 4, 1943 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Strouds Creek and Muddlety Railroad Tioga, West Virginia; Nov. 5, 1920 to Mar. 22, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Sumpter Valley Railway Chicago, [UNK]; Nov. 27, 1918 to Dec. 27, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Suncook Valley Railroad Pittsfield, New [UNK]; Mar. 20, 1924 to Dec. 24, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Susquehanna and New York Railroad Williamsport, Pa; Oct. 13, 1948 to Oct. 16, 1948 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Suwannee Trainferry Lines Florida?; June 10, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Sword's Creek Railway Swords Creek, Virginia; Jan. 3, 1946 to Sept. 11, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Sylvania Central Railway Dublin, Georgia; Mar. 12, 1932 to Mar. 15, 1954 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Talbotton Railroad Talbotton, Georgia; Apr. 2, 1915 to Aug. 15, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Tama and Toledo Railway Ceder Rapids, Iowa; July 24, 1933 to Jan. 15, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Tallulah Falls Railway Correlia, Georgia; June 22, 1920 to Aug. 4, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 22-24)
  - Tavares and Gulf Railroad Norfolk, Virginia; Mar. 9, 1943 to Nov. 2, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, Reports, News clippings
  - Tennessee and North Carolina Railway Hayesville, North Carolina; Mar. 31, 1914 to Dec. 18, 1951 (Box 42, Folder 26-27)
  - Texarkana Stockyards Oklahoma? no reference to location made; Oct. 21, 1949 to Oct. 24, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Texas Electric Railway Dallas, Texas; July 1, 1922 to Jan. 10, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    Report, Correspondence, News clipping
  - Texas Public Utilities Commission Austin, Texas; Apr. 19, 1948 to June 10, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Texas State Railroad owned by Texas State Govt., runs from Palenstine and Rusk, Texas; Sept. 5, 1951 to Dec. 7, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    Reports, News article
  - Texas Short Line Railway runs from Grand Saline to Van, Texas; June 10, 1958 to July 18, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Toledo and Eastern Railroad Alliance Ohio and Toledo, Ohio; Sept. 27, 1935 to July 15, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Toledo Terminal Railroad Toledo, Ohio; Apr. 12, 1926 to Oct. 22, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Trans-Florida Central Railroad Fellsmere, Florida; Oct. 11, 1913 to July 13, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Tremont and Gulf Railway Winnfield, Louisiana; Aug. 14, 1933 to June 3, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    Reports, Correspondence, Map
  - Unadilla Valley Railway New Berlin, New York; Mar. 11, 1919 to Jan. 16, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 10-11)
    Correspondence, Reports, Drawing
  - Union Stockyard and Transit Company Chicago, [UNK]; Jan. 15, 1953 to 12, 1910=57 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Valley Railroad McKean County, Pennsylvania; Feb. 5, 1947 to Aug. 13, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Verde Tunnel and Smelter Railroad Clarkdale, Arizona; Sept. 1, 1921 to May 7, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 14-16)
    Reports, Correspondence, Testimony, Exhibits
  - Virginian Railway Norfolk, Virginia; Dec. 9, 1948 to Nov. 27, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    Reports, Correspondence, Brochure
  - Virginia and Truckee Railway Carson City, Nevada; Dec. 9, 1918 to May 13, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 18-21)
    Reports, Correspondence, News article, Brochure
  - Volunteer Portland Cement no reference made to location; Mar. 8, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Waco, Beaumont, Trinity and Sabine Railway Trinity Texas; July 20, 1933 to Nov. 14, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Walla, Walla Valley Railway Seattle, Washington; Mar. 4, 1919 to Mar. 11, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Warren and Ouachita Valley Railway Warren, Arkansas; Apr. 27, 1917 to Apr. 15, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    Correspondence, Time table, Legislative bill
  - Washington, Brandywine and Point Lookout Railroad (U.S. Navy M gt.) Brandy [UNK], Maryland; Jan. 13, 1954 to Dec. 14, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Waterloo Railroad Waterloo, Iowa; Feb. 11, 1918 to Mar. 18, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 2-3)
  - Waterloo, Cedar Falls and Northern Railroad Waterloo, Iowa; Apr. 12, 1956 to Jan. 13, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Weatherford, Mineral Wells and Northwestern Railway Dallas, Texas; Dec. 27, 1932 to June 16, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Weldwood Railroad Fairhaven, Calif; Dec. 5, 1958 to Jan. 8, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Westvaco Railroad green River, Wyoming; Mar. 17, 1953 to June 8, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - West Palm Beach Terminal Company West Palm Beach, Florida; Apr. 6, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - West Pittstown - Exeter Railroad Scranton, Penna; Aug. 3, 1925 to June 26, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Western Allegheny Railroad Pittsburg, Pennsylvania runs from Dewey to Queen Junction, Pa; May 2, 1911 to Nov. 11, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Wharton and Northern Railroad Wharton, New Jersey; May 3, 1960 to Feb. 17, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Wichita Falls and Southern Railroad Wichita Falls, Texas; June 16, 1920 to Jan. 12, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, Reports, News articles
  - Willamina and Grand Ronde Railway Longview, Washington; Nov. 17, 1937 to Jan. 5, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Winchester and Western Railroad Winchester, Virginia; May 7, 1949 to June 28, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Winona Railroad Warsaw, Indiana; Feb. 1, 1923 to Apr. 29, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Wisconsin Power and Light Co. Madison, Wisconsin; Feb. 14, 1927 to Jan. 39, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Wisconsin Central Railway Co. Minnesota? principal line runs from Minneapolis-St. Paul to Chicago, Illinois; Mar. 17, 1952 to Sept. 3, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Wyoming Railway Co. Ceder Rapids, Iowa, moved to Cheyenne, Wyoming; Jan. 9, 1919 to Sept. 30, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Yadkin Railroad Hickory, North Carolina; June 2, 1920 to June 7, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Yakima Valley Transportation Co. Yakima, Wash; Mar. 28, 1919 to Apr. 2, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 20)